[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120720pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "VBN", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 51, "question": "What was the first that you knew that this was going down?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "VBD", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 52, "answer": "You -- the first thing that happened is he came in through the exit door, through, you know, what is being said is tear gas.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120720pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "PDT", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 63, "question": "Governor Hickenlooper?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 64, "answer": "So this has been a long day and I appreciate how long a day it's been for all of you in the media.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Hickenlooper"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120720pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 195, "question": "Has he said anything about why he did this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 196, "answer": "If we have information about a motive, we will not share it with you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120720pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 198, "question": "He's talking to you though?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 199, "answer": "I won't talk about his admissions.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120720pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 201, "question": "(INAUDIBLE) that perfectly legal?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 202, "answer": "My understanding is all the weapons he possessed, he possessed legally.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120720pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 239, "question": "What about the mask?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 240, "answer": "It was a gas mask.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120720pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 314, "question": "Did you realize at the time you've been hit by a bullet?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 315, "answer": "Well, at the -- I did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120720pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", ",", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "VBG", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 322, "question": "Could you see him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 323, "answer": "No, I was in the middle -- I ended up on the row over, and then I ended up crawling out.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120720pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 347, "question": "What is your reaction to the fact that this young man was legally able in the last two months to obtain four weapons, including an assault rifle, and so much ammunition and commit this atrocity?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "CD", "NNS", ",", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", "RB", "NN", "CC", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 348, "answer": "It's -- it's not right.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["last two months"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120720pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ":", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 358, "question": "Jamie, did you think that you were going to get out alive or did you fear that everyone was going to die in there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 359, "answer": "No, this -- my thought was this is how it ends.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120720pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 473, "question": "What kind of boy was he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 474, "answer": "He's a quiet guy, you know, very nice.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120720pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "TO", "PRP$", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "."], "qSentId": 481, "question": "Have you been able to speak to her today?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBN", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 482, "answer": "No, I haven't been able to talk to her because too many people tried to get her.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120720pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 496, "question": "And would stricter gun control have made a difference in this case?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "MD", "VB", "NN", "NN", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 497, "answer": "First of all, I want to express my grief and my deep condolences for the victims.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120720pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 523, "question": "What is your reaction to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 524, "answer": "Honestly, Piers, I think this is the wrong night to be doing this.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120720pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 550, "question": "Given what has happened today, do you think there is now legitimate cause to press politicians for tougher gun control in America?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 551, "answer": "Piers, I think, like you said, that legitimate cause existed yesterday.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120720pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNP", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "TO", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 575, "question": "That can't be right, can it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 576, "answer": "The American people need to express their outrage directly to their representatives on every single level.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120720pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 603, "question": "What was your reaction to what happened?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "WP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 604, "answer": "Well, it did bring back some terrible memories.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120720pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 629, "question": "Do you think that Washington is going to wake up tomorrow, perhaps, and realize that America simply can't keep having this number of outrages involving guns?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "CC", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "RB", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 630, "answer": "Well, I think any decision of serious political issues or policy issues are not going to be had now.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Washington", "America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120720pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 655, "question": "What are your feelings about what's happened here today?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBN", "RB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 656, "answer": "First of all, thanks a lot.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]